digitalcamerawarehouse.com.au 2010-07-26

# Privacy Policy - Digital Camera Warehouse

| 

Home | Visit us | Delivery | Duty Free | FAQs | Feedback | Gov't/Schools | Contact us | View Cart

****All DCW cameras come with Genuine Australian Warranties. Cheap Prices and Fast Delivery!****

**Privacy Policy**

Digital Camera warehouse (DCW) is committed to safeguarding personal privacy. Unless given consent to do otherwise, DCW will only collect and use personal information as set out below.

When a product is purchased personal information may be requested (such as name, address, email, phone numbers) in order to process and deliver your order, and to advise of other related products which may be of interest. We will not reveal your personal information to any external organisation except where necessary for the purpose of fulfilling your order (e.g. financial institutions that issued your credit card and courier companies that deliver your order). 

Personal Information will be used for the following purposes:

  * To enable your order to be processed according to DCW procedures. 
  * To render services related to DCW business such as warranty or after sales services. 
  * To provide you with information about products, service and/or special offers. 
  * To obtain opinions or comments about products and/or services. 
  * To record statistical data for marketing analysis.

DCW recognises the trust with which individuals provide personal information, and such information will not be used or disclosed for any other purposes than those given above without your consent, except in exceptional cases when disclosure may be required by law or is necessary to protect the rights or property of DCW, or any member of the public.

DCW may contact individuals using the information which was provided by them in order to: 

  * Enable your order to be processed according to DCW procedures 
  * Provide information about new products, special offers and other matters relating to your purchase or digital cameras that may be of interest. 
  * To send newsletters about digital cameras, tips or information about digital photography, or related matters.

If an individual receives communications from DCW which they do not wish to receive, they may remove their name from our contact database by emailing [ unsubscribe@digitalcamerawarehouse.com.au](mailto:unsubscribe@digitalcamerawarehouse.com.au)  Please allow 14 days for this request to be processed. ** **

DCW will endeavour to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any personal information recorded, and to keep this information accurate and up to date. The information is stored on secure servers if in digital format, or in locked areas if in hardcopy format. DCW employees are obliged to respect the confidentiality of any personal information held by DCW. However, security of communications over the Internet cannot be guaranteed, and therefore absolute assurance that information will be secure at all times cannot be given. DCW will not be held responsible for events arising from unauthorised access to personal information. 

DCW provides links to web sites outside of the DCW site. These linked sites are not under the control of DCW, and DCW is not responsible for the conduct of companies linked to the DCW web site. 

Inquiries relating to our Privacy Policy, or any problems or complaints may be directed to the General Manager by calling the customer service number 1300 365 220. 

Digital Camera Warehouse delivers cheap discount digital cameras Australia wide.     
Delivery to Sydney, Brisbane, Adelaide, Melbourne, Perth, Hobart, Darwin, Canberra is usually 1-3 days if in stock.   
Delivery to regional areas is usually 2-5 days for items in stock. Let us know if we can help you.  
For our best price buy online or [ **visit a DCW  camera shop in **](http://www.digitalcamerawarehouse.com.au/webcontent36.htm) [ **Brisbane,**](http://www.digitalcamerawarehouse.com.au/webcontent36.htm) [ **Sydney** **or Melbourne**.](http://www.digitalcamerawarehouse.com.au/webcontent36.htm)

**[ About us](http://www.digitalcamerawarehouse.com.au/webcontent43.htm)** **|** [ Delivery charges](http://www.digitalcamerawarehouse.com.au/webcontent98.htm) **|  **[Duty Free](http://www.digitalcamerawarehouse.com.au/webcontent32.htm) **  | [ FAQs](http://www.digitalcamerawarehouse.com.au/webcontent42.htm) |**[Terms of use](http://www.digitalcamerawarehouse.com.au/webcontent58.htm) **  | ** [ Warranty](http://www.digitalcamerawarehouse.com.au/webcontent45.htm) **  | ** [ Returns](http://www.digitalcamerawarehouse.com.au/webcontent64.htm) **  | ** [ Privacy Policy](http://www.digitalcamerawarehouse.com.au/webcontent65.htm) **  | [ Reviews](http://www.digitalcamerawarehouse.com.au/category197_1.htm) | ** [ Testimonials](http://www.digitalcamerawarehouse.com.au/webcontent31.htm) **  | ** [ Tech Support](http://www.digitalcamerawarehouse.com.au/webcontent74.htm) **** **Copyright  © 2001- 2008 Digital Camera Warehouse Pty Ltd. **** ABN:96 244 920 534. All rights reserved.   
****All brands, logos, images  and names are trademarks of their respective companies.  
Images used are for illustrative purposes only and may not be identical to the product supplied.**  
  
---|---
